#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/t-knguyen (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Statistical Data Analysis
Data Classification
Data Fusion

# Nguyen Trung-Kien

Al Researcher at Cinnamon Al

Vietnam

## Summary

I'm interested in Al application (Machine Learning/Deep Learning field)

I had some experiences in the image processing works, especially in detection, classification and segmentation problematics. These works based on different types of data, from acoustic signal to SONAR and hyper-spectral image.

At this moment, I'm working on the DL applications in document text (printed and writing) such as data generation, text recognition via the supervised, semi-supervised frameworks (Convolution net - CNN, GCN; Auto Encoder - VAE, AAE; Generative model - GAN).

PS: I'm also an amateur in photography. Here are some photos (https://500px.com/ngtrkn)

# Experience

Cinnamon Al

Al Researcher

October 2018 - Present (6 years 6 months)

Text recognition (printed and handwriting) with deep learning approaches (supervised/semi-supervised frameworks; convolution net - CNN, GCN; Auto encoder - VAE, AAE; Generative model - GAN)

Tools: python-pytorch

**IMT** Atlantique

Postdoctoral Researcher

March 2018 - September 2018 (7 months)

Brest Area, France

Detection of leaking sources in drinking water system via acoustic hydrophones.

Keywords: anormal detection, information fusion, source localisation.

Tools: Matlab

iXBlue

PHD

March 2014 - July 2017 (3 years 5 months)

Brest Area, France

Multi-beam echo-sounder (MBES), Classification, Texture analyse, Decision Fusion

Actimar

Stagaire

March 2013 - September 2013 (7 months)

Hyperspectral image, classification

### Education

Télécom Bretagne (ex- ENSTB, école nationale supérieure des télécommunications de Bretagne)

Master's degree, Image processing · (2012 - 2013)

Télécom Bretagne (ex- ENSTB, école nationale supérieure des télécommunications de Bretagne)

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Image processing · (2011 - 2013)